storycartel.com 2016-12-26

# Privacy Policy

as of 10/19/12

Story Cartel respects the trust our registered users and other visitors have in us. Therefore, this online Privacy Policy tells you about the information Story Cartel collects through the features and services available on storycartel.com (the “Site”), and how we use that information.

By using our services and accessing our Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy, as modified from time to time by us.

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a new policy on our Site and change the date at the top of the policy. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our Privacy Policy whenever you visit this Site for any updates or changes.

## Information About You

The following details the types of information we collect and how we use it.

We collect several types of information on our Site. We do not knowingly collect, however, any information from children under 13 years of age, nor are our services designed for use by children under 13.

We collect, store, and will share with authors whose books are included in our services “Personally Identifiable Information,” which generally means information that can be used to identify you individually, such as your name, your electronic mail address, and information about your reading preferences.

We collect, store, and will share with authors whose books are included in our services ”Non-Personally Identifiable Information,” which generally means information about you that does not identify you personally or individually such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type and click stream data.

We collect, store, and will share with authors whose books are included in our services ”Aggregate Information,” which is information about use of our Site, such as pages visited on our Site. The information we collect depends on what services and features you use on our Site.  
The following details the types of information we collect and how we use it.

You can, however, opt-out from inclusion in our collection of information by emailing us directly at [info@storycartel.com](mailto:info@storycartel.com) or the authors whose books are included in our services collection of information, by contacting them directly through their web-services.

## Registration with Story Cartel and Transactional Data

When you register on our Site, you are required to submit an e-mail address (which is your User ID for the Site) additional personal information. We also collect and store access information related to your account.

We use your e-mail address to provide you with the book you’ve requested to download. By providing your e-mail address to us, you agree that we may, from time to time, contact you by e-mail regarding the book or other materials you have accessed or downloaded from our Site. If you do not wish to receive such e-mails you will have the ability to opt-out.

We do not use your email address or other Personally Identifiable Information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes such as notifying you of major Site changes or for customer service purposes.

We use both your Personally Identifiable Information and certain Non-Personally-Identifiable Information to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.

We may share your Personally Identifiable Information and certain Non-Personally-Identifiable with authors and related publishing industry professionals promoted through the services of the Site.

## Security

Story Cartel takes commercially reasonable precautions to safeguard your information against theft and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or our use of your information you can e-mail us at [info@storycartel.com](mailto:info@storycartel.com).
